class Quizzes {
  static final oopQuiz1 = [
    {
      'question': 'A blueprint or template defining the structure and behavior of objects.',
      'answer': 'Class',
    },
    {
      'question': 'A self-contained unit combining properties and methods to represent a specific data type.',
      'answer': 'Object',
    },
    {
      'question': 'This is similar to a method that is cited when an object of the class is created.',
      'answer': 'Constructors',
    },
    {
      'question': 'A procedure or function associated with a class, defining specific actions objects can perform.',
      'answer': 'Methods',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Are methods used to protect your data and make your code more secure.',
      'answer': 'Getters/Setters',
    },
    {
      'question': 'This is a block of code that performs a specific task.',
      'answer': 'Methods',
    },
    {
      'question': 'How do you access members of a class in OOP?',
      'answer': 'Using the dot (.) operator or Period',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the naming convention typically used for getter methods?',
      'answer': 'get',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the naming convention typically used for setter methods?',
      'answer': 'set',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is a programming concept that works on the principle that objects are the most important part of your program.',
      'answer': 'Object Oriented Programming',
    },
  ];

  static final oopQuiz2 = [
    {
      'question': 'Which access modifier restricts visibility to only within the class itself?',
      'answer': 'Private',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Which access modifier makes declarations visible everywhere?',
      'answer': 'Public',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Yes or No, can constructors be inherited by subclasses in Java?',
      'answer': 'No',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What keyword is used to call the constructor of the superclass from a subclass?',
      'answer': 'super',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What keyword is used to call out the ParentClass?',
      'answer': 'extends',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Which access modifier makes declarations are visible within the package or all subclasses',
      'answer': 'Protected',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Which access modifier makes declarations are visible only within the package.',
      'answer': 'Default/None',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'These are used to set the accessibility(visibility) of classes, variables, methods, constructors, data members, and the setter methods.',
      'answer': 'Access Modifiers',
    },
    {
      'question': 'A class that is derived from another class is called?',
      'answer': 'subclass',
    },
    {
      'question': 'The class from which the subclass is derived is called?',
      'answer': 'superclass',
    },
  ];

  static final dbmsQuiz1 = [
    {
      'question': 'Entity-relationship (E-R) model was introduced by Chen in what year?',
      'answer': '1976',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is the information or data which is stored in attributes of any entity.',
      'answer': 'Value',
    },
    {
      'question': 'An attribute having only single value for a particular entity',
      'answer': 'Single Valued Attribute',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is the function of any entity which it plays in relationship set.',
      'answer': 'Role',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is an attribute or set of attributes that is used to identify data in entity sets.',
      'answer': 'Key',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'It is the language used for both data definition and data manipulation. It is one of the most popular database languages currently in use in the industry.',
      'answer': 'Structured Query Language or SQL',
    },
    {
      'question':
          'It is used to define database structure or pattern. It is used to create schema, tables, indexes, constraints, etc. in the database.',
      'answer': 'Data Definition Language or DDL',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is used to run the changes made by the DML statement.',
      'answer': 'Transaction Control Language or TCL',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is used to retrieve the stored or saved data. It also has rollback parameters.',
      'answer': 'Data Control Language or DCL',
    },
    {
      'question': 'It is used for accessing and manipulating data in a database. It handles user requests.',
      'answer': 'Data Manipulation Language or DML',
    },
  ];

  static final dbmsQuiz2 = [
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we will create a table:',
      'answer': 'create table',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we want to add another field?',
      'answer': 'alter table add column',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we want to add values on the record?',
      'answer': 'insert into set AND/OR insert into values',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command to delete a field inside a table?',
      'answer': 'alter table drop',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command to add primary key?',
      'answer': 'alter table add primary key',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command display list of tables in a database?',
      'answer': 'show tables',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we want to add field with specific location in the table?',
      'answer': 'alter table add after AND/OR alter table add first',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we want to delete fieldname?',
      'answer': 'alter table drop',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we want to create a database?',
      'answer': 'create database',
    },
    {
      'question': 'What is the command if we want to show the table structure?',
      'answer': 'describe',
    },
  ];
}
